Clearly, the Spanish authorities have every right to try and investigate these matters further. General Augusto Pinochet, who ruled Chile as a despot for 17 years, has been arrested in London after Spain asked that he be extradited for the presumed murders of hundreds of Chilean and Spanish citizens, the British authorities announced on 10/17/1998. General Augusto Pinochet, the former Chilean dictator arrested here at the request of a Spanish judge, remained sequestered under police guard on 10/18/1998, awaiting a potentially devastating court hearing to weigh his extradition on charges of genocide, terrorism and murder.