Former Chilean dictator General Augusto Pinochet has been arrested by British police on a Spanish extradition warrant, despite protests from Chile that he is entitled to diplomatic immunity. Augusto Pinochet is being called to account by Spanish authorities for the deaths, detention and torture of political opponents. Pinochet, who ousted elected President Salvador Allende in a bloody 1973 coup, remained commander-in-chief of the Chilean army until March. Since the case against Pinochet began at Madrid’s National Court, the United States has agreed to provide the Spanish judges with documents related to human rights violations under the Pinochet regime.