All of these satellites came through Tuesday’s meteor shower unscathed. Showers of Leonid meteors may produce hundreds or thousands of blazing meteors each hour. Some satellites in low-earth orbits can actually hide from meteoroid storms, Ozkul said. The scientists who track Temple-Tuttle do not even call it a shower, they call it a meteor storm. Satellite experts said that some damage might take days to detect, but that satellites generally seemed to have escaped disabling harm. This storm of meteors, called Leonid meteors because they come from the direction of constellation Leo, will be the first to hit the Earth since 1966 when the world's space programs were in their infancy, and its effects on satellite systems are uncertain.