Taking a major step toward statehood, the Palestinians on Tuesday inaugurated Gaza International Airport, their first gateway to the world, with cheers, tears and an outpouring of patriotism. The first Palestinian commercial flight landed at Amman’s Marka Airport on Saturday, inaugurating an air route between Jordan and the autonomous Gaza Strip. Established in 1996, the tiny Palestinian airline was an outgrowth of the accords with Israel on Palestinian self-rule. Israel has threatened to close down the Palestinian-run Gaza airport over a security violation, an Israeli official said Tuesday, a move that could further undermine the already fragile peace process.