Turkey has amassed troops on the border with Syria and warned of a military confrontation following allegations that Syria is supporting Turkish Kurdish rebels. For its part, Turkey is complaining ever more loudly about Syria’s support for Kurdish insurgents in Turkey. Turkey amassed troops, pick up 4th graf pvs Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak flew to Damascus on Sunday to try to defuse growing tension between Syria and Turkey. On Saturday, Defense Minister Ismet Sezgin said Turkey would soon carry out an exercise near the Syrian border, private NTV television reported. Turkish generals began issuing public warnings to Syria last month.