Tensions between Turkey and Syria have reached a point causing the top Turkish military commander to say they have reached a state of undeclared war. Turkey accuses Syria of supporting Kurdish rebels in Turkey, a charge denied by Syria. Syria is angry over Turkey’s closer ties to Israel and alleges that Turkey, by building dams on the Euphrates River, threatens its water supply. Egypt’s President Mubarak has visited Saudi Arabia and Damascus and plans to continue to Ankara hoping to defuse the crisis. Israel claims no part in the tension. Turkey has attacked Kurdish bases in Iraq and threatens those in Syria.