A stubbornly independent judge who more than once has challenged the Spanish government, Baltasar Garzon was ridiculed when he first set out to pursue the most notorious right-wing generals in South America for human rights crimes committed in the 1970s and ’80s, offenses for which they had already been granted amnesty at home. He said the case seemed to be unprecedented and unusual. An influential lawmaker from the governing Labor Party on Saturday backed Spanish requests to question former Chilean dictator General Augusto Pinochet, in London for back surgery, on allegations of genocide and terrorism.