Peppered the atmosphere with tiny bits of space junk zipping along at 155,000 mph (250,000 kph). Clouds interfered with the view from many sites, but many stargazers were rewarded with a spectacular view of meteors streaking through the skies in blazes of red and white as the Leonid meteor shower reached its climax early Wednesday in Asia. The shower is caused by the Earth's passage through the long tail of the Comet Tempel-Tuttle. By the time the earth collides with a dense swarm of meteoroids Tuesday night to unleash what may be the heaviest meteor bombardment since 1966, many orbiting satellites will have maneuvered into positions facing away from the storm to avoid damage.