President Hosni Mubarak of Egypt will go to Syria and Turkey to help cool tensions between the two countries, which appear to be edging toward a military conflict. Signaling it does not want to be involved in any potential military confrontation between Syria and Turkey, Israel is limiting routine exercises along its own border with Syria. For its part, Turkey is complaining ever more loudly about Syria’s support for Kurdish insurgents in Turkey. Turkey’s military-dominated National Security Council discussed problems with Syria on Wednesday, and announced afterward that Turkey was considering imposing economic, political and military sanctions against Syria.