People in East Asia, however, will have ringside seats, and if skies are clear, they are likely to witness a great meteor display under ideal conditions: a dark, moonless night. Some people think the Leonid storm this year will be as good as the one in 1966, which was the best one this century, but we think the 1998 shower will be more modest perhaps something between 200 and 5,000 meteors per hour. Astrophysicists, atmospheric scientists and others have been readying their experiments for a year or more in preparation for Tuesday night’s expected Leonid Meteor storm.