The Spanish authorities contend that Pinochet may have committed crimes against Spanish citizens in Chile. Former Chilean dictator General Augusto Pinochet has been arrested by British police on a Spanish extradition warrant, despite protests from Chile that he is entitled to diplomatic immunity. Baltasar Garzon, one of two Spanish magistrates handling probes into human rights violations in Chile and Argentina, filed a request to question Pinochet on Wednesday. But Britain said Pinochet did not have diplomatic immunity. Chile said, graf 3 pvs President Fidel Castro said Sunday he disagreed with the arrest in London of former Chilean dictator Augusto Pinochet, calling it a case of international meddling.