An arctic cold wave, the worst in 10 years, hit parts of Europe, bringing sub-zero temperatures and killing scores of people. Hardest hit were Poland, Bulgaria, and Romania as well as parts of central and eastern France. In Poland, three weeks of sub-zero temperatures killed at least 85 people in November, 29 more than in all of the previous winter. Most of the victims were homeless whose deaths by exposure were alcohol related. Blizzards and cold temperatures also hit Bulgaria and Romania, stranding hundreds in their cars. Elsewhere, snow blanketed the Italian island of Capri for the first time in 10 years.