President Joseph Estrada on Saturday urged militant unionists at Philippine Airlines to accept a vote by workers approving a 10-year no-strike deal to revive the debt-laden airline. President Joseph Estrada said Saturday the financially troubled Philippine Airlines will resume its international flights on Sunday by flying him to Singapore where he will address the World Economic Forum. Philippine Airlines said Thursday it will attempt to rebuild alone after Hong Kong’s Cathay Pacific Airlines pulled out of talks on acquiring a stake in the ailing Philippine flag carrier. A strike by employees precipitated the airline’s near-death experience in September, when Tan shut down the carrier after its unions refused to accept a drastic cost-cutting plan.