It already has claimed 20 more lives than the number of cold-related deaths in all of last winter, police say two more victims of Poland’s prolonged cold front were found Thursday, raising the death toll from more than two weeks of freezing temperatures to at least 74. One man was injured by a falling icicle, but he was not hospitalized. The weather played a role in at least 24 deaths in Romania and Bulgaria over the past three days. An Arctic cold wave that hit Poland a week ago has killed 32 people, police said Monday.