The charges that Wang faces, in a trial that will almost certainly be secret and quick, could bring a sentence of five years or more. A Chinese dissident fleeing a new round of arrests of democracy activists in Shanghai arrived here on 12/09/1998 and announced that he and other opponents of the Chinese government plan a demonstration on 12/09/1998 at the United Nations to protest the crackdown. Last week the Chinese government arrested 10 members and sympathizers of the China Democracy Party, one of whom, Wang Youcai, is to go on trial December 17.