After months of noisy prelude, the antitrust trial against the Microsoft Corporation opened in federal court Monday morning with a pointed personal attack on Bill Gates, the company’s chairman. Microsoft, the world’s leading maker of computer software, said demand for the Windows 98 operating-system exceeded its projections, particularly in Japan and Europe. A lawyer for Microsoft Corporation on Thursday portrayed the company's competitor in the Internet software business, Netscape Communications Corporation, as a willing and eager participant in deal-making that culminated in a June 1995 meeting at which the government and Netscape now say that Microsoft illegally offered to divide the market.