In a recent move that indicated he has no intention of backing away from his company’s aggressive business tactics, Microsoft Corporation’s chairman, Bill Gates, has proposed acquiring the software business behind 3Com Corporation’s popular Palm Pilot hand-held computer, according to people who have been briefed on the discussions. The antitrust suit, initiated last October, originally focused on Microsoft’s linking of its Internet Explorer World Wide Web browser with the industry-dominant Windows 95 operating system. Microsoft replies that the prosecutors are misinterpreting a routine business meeting. Demonstrating yet again the power of its franchise, the Microsoft Corporation.