An Arctic cold wave and accompanying blizzards have killed at least 65 people throughout Europe, police and media reported Monday. Temperatures in central and eastern Poland over the weekend were as low as minus 20 degrees Celsius (minus 4 Fahrenheit). Temperatures have dropped well below freezing, with minus 26 Celsius (minus 4 Fahrenheit) recorded in Poland on Sunday. The death toll from almost three weeks of sub-zero temperatures reached 85 on Saturday, after two men froze to death in their unheated homes in northeastern Poland.