Turkey’s president began trying to construct a new government on 11/25/1998 but the pieces do not neatly fit: pro-Islamic forces pressing for power and their military-backed, Western-style opponents struggling to unite. President Suleyman Demirel opened talks with party leaders just hours after the corruption-battered coalition of Prime Minister Mesut Yilmaz lost a confidence vote in parliament. One of Turkey’s leading politicians warned on 11/29/1998 that a political vacuum could cripple the domestic battle to keep Islamists at bay and in the fight abroad for the extradition of a Kurdish rebel leader.