An Arctic cold wave and accompanying blizzards have killed at least 65 people throughout Europe, police and media reported on 11/23/1998. Croatia reported its first cold-related death on 11/25/1998, a woman who lived alone in an unheated house. The death toll from almost three weeks of sub-zero temperatures has reached 83, after a homeless man froze to death in a Warsaw park. Poland’s extreme cold began November 16, with temperatures dropping to minus 26 Celsius (minus 4 Fahrenheit).