Qin, 44, and Wang, 31, are accused of inciting the subversion of state power, apparently for helping to organize the China Democracy Party. Wang argued that his activities were legal under China’s constitution and under an international covenant on political rights that China has signed, Ms Hu said. As the founder of the suppressed new political party, the China Democracy Party, he publicly announced its charter in June during President Clinton’s visit to China. He said he had no information from Chinese authorities about Qin or Wang. Three other Democratic Party organizers were also detained on Monday, although two of them were released early Wednesday.