The Islamic party, Virtue, is the largest party in parliament. Last year, the military ousted Turkey’s first Islamic-led government. Acting Deputy Premier Bulent Ecevit on Sunday called on Turkey’s two center-right parties, led by arch-rivals acting Prime Minister Mesut Yilmaz and former Premier Tansu Ciller, to join him in a governing coalition. The no-confidence vote has dragged Turkey into grave political chaos, Yilmaz declared. Within hours of the government’s collapse, Virtue leader Recai Kutan met with President Suleyman Demirel, who is charged with picking a political leader who can command a governing majority in Parliament.