Poland’s extreme cold began November 16, with temperatures dropping to minus 26 Celsius (minus 4 Fahrenheit). In Poland, 32 people died, most of them homeless or others who passed out in the cold after drinking alcohol, police said. An Arctic cold wave and accompanying blizzards have killed at least 62 people throughout Europe, police and media reported Monday. Temperatures in central and eastern Poland over the weekend were as low as minus 20 degrees Celsius (minus 4 Fahrenheit). Two more victims of Poland’s prolonged cold front were found Thursday, raising the death toll from more than two weeks of freezing temperatures to at least 74. Police said a 40-year-old man was found frozen to death in central Poland on Thursday morning.